[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 8, "question": "(on camera) You're quite a naughty girl, aren't you, Vanessa?", "question_tokens": ["(", "on", "camera", ")", "You", "'re", "quite", "a", "naughty", "girl", ",", "are", "n't", "you", ",", "Vanessa", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 9, "answer": "Naughty - fertile, maybe, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Naughty", "-", "fertile", ",", "maybe", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Vanessa"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "What do I have no idea about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "I", "have", "no", "idea", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "The title of the book originally came to me because I had gotten some interested about doing a memoir for years.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "title", "of", "the", "book", "originally", "came", "to", "me", "because", "I", "had", "gotten", "some", "interested", "about", "doing", "a", "memoir", "for", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "What are you thinking when it all starts erupting like this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "thinking", "when", "it", "all", "starts", "erupting", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Well, there was a large part that was fantastic and positive and overwhelming.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "was", "a", "large", "part", "that", "was", "fantastic", "and", "positive", "and", "overwhelming", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Do you feel you achieved that goal?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "you", "achieved", "that", "goal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Yes, partly.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "partly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 133, "question": "Do you feel like a little part of you has constantly been having to prove people wrong?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "like", "a", "little", "part", "of", "you", "has", "constantly", "been", "having", "to", "prove", "people", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "But there's no pressure, you know, when you're always underestimated -", "answer_tokens": ["But", "there", "'s", "no", "pressure", ",", "you", "know", ",", "when", "you", "'re", "always", "underestimated", "-"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "Satisfying, too, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Satisfying", ",", "too", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", ",", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "ILLIAMS: Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["ILLIAMS", ":", "Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "Why didn't you listen to your mum?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "n't", "you", "listen", "to", "your", "mum", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "Because I'm a rebel.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "'m", "a", "rebel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "You weren't quite what your teachers thought, were you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "n't", "quite", "what", "your", "teachers", "thought", ",", "were", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "WP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "You have no idea.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "have", "no", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "That was a great part, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "was", "a", "great", "part", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "I loved Wilhelmina.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "loved", "Wilhelmina", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "The stuff you dream of, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["The", "stuff", "you", "dream", "of", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "ILLIAMS: I think so, wearing fabulous clothing and bossing people around.", "answer_tokens": ["ILLIAMS", ":", "I", "think", "so", ",", "wearing", "fabulous", "clothing", "and", "bossing", "people", "around", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "When did you have that conversation?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "you", "have", "that", "conversation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Actually, we never had it.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "we", "never", "had", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "So your mother read it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "your", "mother", "read", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Read it, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Read", "it", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "When your mother read it, what did she say to you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "your", "mother", "read", "it", ",", "what", "did", "she", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "She didn't say anything.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "did", "n't", "say", "anything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "You haven't had any contact again?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "n't", "had", "any", "contact", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Of all the things that you did, what made him the proudest, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Of", "all", "the", "things", "that", "you", "did", ",", "what", "made", "him", "the", "proudest", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "JJS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Oh, I would say Broadway because he knew that that was my dream.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "would", "say", "Broadway", "because", "he", "knew", "that", "that", "was", "my", "dream", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "POS", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "What did he say to you afterwards?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "he", "say", "to", "you", "afterwards", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "We had a reception at my parents' house, and he just said that he was very proud and he knew that I accomplished a dream.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "had", "a", "reception", "at", "my", "parents", "'", "house", ",", "and", "he", "just", "said", "that", "he", "was", "very", "proud", "and", "he", "knew", "that", "I", "accomplished", "a", "dream", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Because there's no escaping, is there?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "there", "'s", "no", "escaping", ",", "is", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "No escaping.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "escaping", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "Do you think you would have had the platform to realize your dreams?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "would", "have", "had", "the", "platform", "to", "realize", "your", "dreams", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "Were you slightly stigmatized by what happened?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "slightly", "stigmatized", "by", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Oh, very stigmatized.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "very", "stigmatized", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "I don't think slightly.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "slightly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "What did your dad say to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "your", "dad", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "My dad - I was in hiding.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "dad", "-", "I", "was", "in", "hiding", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Why try and hide what's happened?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "try", "and", "hide", "what", "'s", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NN", "CC", "VB", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "You know, I knew my parents were there.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "knew", "my", "parents", "were", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Was it any comfort to you that it was a massively successful publication, the Vanessa Williams nude pictures?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "any", "comfort", "to", "you", "that", "it", "was", "a", "massively", "successful", "publication", ",", "the", "Vanessa", "Williams", "nude", "pictures", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Vanessa Williams"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "It's getting sad.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "getting", "sad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Well, you've written about it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "'ve", "written", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "I've been through the same, so I know that that in the end is the glue, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "been", "through", "the", "same", ",", "so", "I", "know", "that", "that", "in", "the", "end", "is", "the", "glue", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "How many times would you say you've been properly in love?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "would", "you", "say", "you", "'ve", "been", "properly", "in", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "Oh, boy.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "boy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "And you married two of them?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "married", "two", "of", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "Or am I making an assumption there?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "am", "I", "making", "an", "assumption", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "Well, I do mention in the book that the two marriages that I ended up getting married to - I was pregnant both times that I got married.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "mention", "in", "the", "book", "that", "the", "two", "marriages", "that", "I", "ended", "up", "getting", "married", "to", "-", "I", "was", "pregnant", "both", "times", "that", "I", "got", "married", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "You're quite a naughty girl, aren't you, Vanessa?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "quite", "a", "naughty", "girl", ",", "are", "n't", "you", ",", "Vanessa", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "Naughty - fertile, maybe, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Naughty", "-", "fertile", ",", "maybe", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Vanessa"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "Have you matured fully, or are you still slightly naughty?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "matured", "fully", ",", "or", "are", "you", "still", "slightly", "naughty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "ILLIAMS: I have nothing going on in my life now, so I have nothing to be naughty about.", "answer_tokens": ["ILLIAMS", ":", "I", "have", "nothing", "going", "on", "in", "my", "life", "now", ",", "so", "I", "have", "nothing", "to", "be", "naughty", "about", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "Would you?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "Yes, I would.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "would", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "You did go out with Robert De Niro?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "go", "out", "with", "Robert", "De", "Niro", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "I went to his house.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "went", "to", "his", "house", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Robert De Niro"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "Is that the same thing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "same", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Do you think it was ever going to be a Broadway thing out of that meeting?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "was", "ever", "going", "to", "be", "a", "Broadway", "thing", "out", "of", "that", "meeting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "If I could find for you now the perfect man based on all you've learned about love, romance, divorce, heartbreak, what would he be like?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "could", "find", "for", "you", "now", "the", "perfect", "man", "based", "on", "all", "you", "'ve", "learned", "about", "love", ",", "romance", ",", "divorce", ",", "heartbreak", ",", "what", "would", "he", "be", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "Available and available for a relationship and not afraid of a relationship.", "answer_tokens": ["Available", "and", "available", "for", "a", "relationship", "and", "not", "afraid", "of", "a", "relationship", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "Is 90 the word you're looking for?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "90", "the", "word", "you", "'re", "looking", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "CD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "Don't say you're 90.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "say", "you", "'re", "90", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Why have you been playing so hard to get?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "have", "you", "been", "playing", "so", "hard", "to", "get", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "I just wanted you to really want me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "wanted", "you", "to", "really", "want", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "HITE: Yes?", "question_tokens": ["HITE", ":", "Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "I want you to kiss my chubby fingers in the way you just did in that clip.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "want", "you", "to", "kiss", "my", "chubby", "fingers", "in", "the", "way", "you", "just", "did", "in", "that", "clip", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "What motivates her to still do this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "motivates", "her", "to", "still", "do", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "PRP$", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "I happen to love what I do for a living.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "happen", "to", "love", "what", "I", "do", "for", "a", "living", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "What is the Betty White magic?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "Betty", "White", "magic", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "It's not magic.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "magic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Betty White"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "Are we still talking professional offers?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "still", "talking", "professional", "offers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "Yes, mostly.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "mostly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 602, "question": "I mean, do you still get men making inappropriate suggestions?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "still", "get", "men", "making", "inappropriate", "suggestions", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "Or is there something else that you don't understand?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "there", "something", "else", "that", "you", "do", "n't", "understand", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "EX", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "Well, actually, there is.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "actually", ",", "there", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "And if so, how old is that top?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "so", ",", "how", "old", "is", "that", "top", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "Oh, it's probably like the rest of my wardrobe.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "it", "'s", "probably", "like", "the", "rest", "of", "my", "wardrobe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 643, "question": "Am I right?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "Yes, well --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 645, "question": "Any nip and tuck ever gone on?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "nip", "and", "tuck", "ever", "gone", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 646, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "Can you believe the way your life has gone, Betty?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "believe", "the", "way", "your", "life", "has", "gone", ",", "Betty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "Crazy, eh?", "question_tokens": ["Crazy", ",", "eh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "And in the middle of all that, there was the love of my life.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "in", "the", "middle", "of", "all", "that", ",", "there", "was", "the", "love", "of", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 697, "question": "I mean, they lasted a combined total of about three years, didn't they?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "they", "lasted", "a", "combined", "total", "of", "about", "three", "years", ",", "did", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "CD", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "Oh, if that.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "if", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Elizabeth Taylor"]}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ":", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "But what was the reality of you and romantic life in those early days?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "was", "the", "reality", "of", "you", "and", "romantic", "life", "in", "those", "early", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "Well, back in those days -- that's why people like Elizabeth Taylor are married so many times.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "back", "in", "those", "days", "--", "that", "'s", "why", "people", "like", "Elizabeth", "Taylor", "are", "married", "so", "many", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 733, "question": "Did you really?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 734, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 740, "question": "Ever since that day have you ever even really looked at another man, or was that -- for you was that it?", "question_tokens": ["Ever", "since", "that", "day", "have", "you", "ever", "even", "really", "looked", "at", "another", "man", ",", "or", "was", "that", "--", "for", "you", "was", "that", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 741, "answer": "As far as falling in love and being in love.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "far", "as", "falling", "in", "love", "and", "being", "in", "love", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Allen Ludden"]}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 748, "question": "What is true love to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "true", "love", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 749, "answer": "Allen Ludden.", "answer_tokens": ["Allen", "Ludden", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 751, "question": "What should women strive to get to to get the love you had?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "women", "strive", "to", "get", "to", "to", "get", "the", "love", "you", "had", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 752, "answer": "It was his enthusiasm.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "his", "enthusiasm", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120421pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 765, "question": "What would he have made of the way your career has just reached this extraordinary plateau?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "he", "have", "made", "of", "the", "way", "your", "career", "has", "just", "reached", "this", "extraordinary", "plateau", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 766, "answer": "He would have been thrilled to pieces.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "would", "have", "been", "thrilled", "to", "pieces", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]